Booth Tarkington Papers, 1812-1956 (bulk 1899-1946): Finding Aid C0062
Manuscripts Division
- Series 1: Writings, 1893-1986; 167 boxes
  - Subseries 1B: Serials, 1941; 11 boxes
    - This Boy Joe, dates not examined; 2 boxes
      - Manuscript, 1935; 4 folders (Box 76, Folder 1-4)
      - Typed Manuscript, dates not examined; 3 folders (Box 76, Folder 5-7)
      - Typed Manuscript, dates not examined; 5 folders (Box 77, Folder 1-5)
    - "A Vatican Sermon": Outline, 1904; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - "Outline Sketch For Consideration", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - "Cassandra Binch" or "Sandy": Manuscript, undated; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 3)
      Never published.
    - "Lydia" or "Elsie": Outline for Serials, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 1C: Short Stories, 1896-1949; 15 boxes
    Consists of manuscripts for short stories written by Booth Tarkington, including "Beasley and the Hunchbergers," "The Fair Coronet," and "The Song of the Bead," as well as others.
    - "Beasley and the Hunchbergers," Cosmopolitan, 1905; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - "The Birth of Thought", undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 79, Folder 2)
      Unpublished.
    - "Captain Schlotterwerz", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - "Clytie's Look": Manuscript and Galleys, Ladies Home Journal, 1926; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - "Constance and Constance," Ladies Home Journal, 1927; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - "Dance Music", 1896; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - "The Dishonorable Dolls," Metropolitan, 1920; 1 folder Autograph manuscript, signed; typed manuscript (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - "The Fair Unfair," Chicago Tribune, 1926; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - "The Fair Coronet", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - "The Street of Bad Children" (Fascinating Stranger Stories): The Red Book Magazine, 1921; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Fascinating Stranger Stories, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - "Filmer's Fascinating Face" (Unpublished), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - "For the Sake of His Own Hide": American Legion Magazine, 1943; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - "For Terrier or Something": Country Life in America, 1914; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - "Francing," Saturday Evening Post, 1925; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - "Girl! Girl! Girl!": from "Seventeen Series", Metropolitan, 1919; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - "Laurence and Roger", "Fascinating Stranger" Story: The Red Book Magazine, 1921; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - "Maud and Bill": Manuscripts, Galley Proofs, "Fascinating Stranger" Story, Everybody's Magazine, 1916; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Penrod Stories: "The Empty House," Metropolitan, 1914; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Penrod Stories: "Sam's Beau," Cosmopolitan, 1917; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Penrod Stories: "Wednesday Madness"(?), Cosmopolitan, 1917; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - "Mr. Brooke": Appleton's Booklovers Magazine, 1905; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - "The Parasite": Saturday Evening Post, 1926; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - "The Power of the Press": McCall's Magazine, 1924; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - "The Property-Man": McClure's Magazine, 1905; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - "Saida Viole": Manuscript and Galleys, Ladies Home Journal, 1926; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - "The Serious Moment": The Flower Mission Magazine, 1899; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - "The Serious Moment", undated; 1 folder Typed manuscripts, some signed (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - "Shanty": Manuscripts and Proof Sheets, Chicago Tribune, 1924; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - "The Song of the Bead", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts, some signed (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - "Stella Crozier": Manuscript and Galleys, Ladies Home Journal, 1925; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - "Thea Zell": The Red Book Magazine, 1925; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - "Young Siblow" (Unpublished), undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - "The World is Mine": The American Magazine, 1944; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Untitled, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - "As the Egg Unlaid": Saturday Evening Post, 1943; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Belinda Dale Stories, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - "Pansy Dale and Patsy" and "Belina Mores": Ladies Home Journal, 1929; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - "Omer's Wife": Ladies Home Journal, 1929; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - "Miss Dale Learns to Laugh": Ladies Home Journal, 1929; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - "Belinda Interferes" and "Belinda's Importance": Ladies Home Journal, 1929-1930; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Captain Valentine Stories, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - "Instrument of Providence": Colliers, 1932; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - "Perilous Strands": Colliers, 1932; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - "The Bravo": Colliers, 1932; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - "Partly A Woman-hater": Red Book Magazine, 1933; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - "Nearest Married": Red Book Magazine, 1934; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - "The Giddabiddy": Red Book Magazine, 1934; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - "Hoop-Te-Do!": Red Book Magazine, 1933; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - "Carola's Causes": Hearst's Inernational and Cosmopolitan, 1930; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - "Cider if Normandy", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - "The Coincidence": McCall's Magazine, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - "Filmer's Fascinating Face", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Fascinating Stranger Stories, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - "Two Hearts That Beat as One": Red Book Magazine, 1922; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - "Renfrew and the New Generation": Red Book Magazine, 1922; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - "Young Love and Younger Crimer": Red Book Magazine, 1922; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - "What Chance Has a Man?": Red Book Magazine, 1922; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - "Here Comes the Pridegroom": Red Book Magazine, 1923; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - "Fifteen": Manuscript, Hearst's International and Cosmopolitan, 1931; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - "Geraldine": Red Book Magazine, 1925; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - "The Hazelberg Twister": Manuscript, Hearst's International and Cosmopolitan, 1949; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - "Henhouse and Calamus": Manuscript (unpublished), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - "Heary The Great": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1936; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - "Home Town Christmas": Manuscript, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - "Instrument of Providence": Manuscript, Colliers, 1932; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - "Mitzi Still Lives": Manuscript, Ladies Home Journal, 1934; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - "Mothuh": Manuscript, Hearst's Internatinal and Cosmopolitan, 1931; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - "Musckickodee": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1929; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - "My Heart": Ladies Home Journal, 1924; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - "Oh, Button Your Coat!": Manuscript, Ladies Home Journal, 1934; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - "Other People's Children": Manuscript, American Magazine, 1930; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - "The Price of Peace": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1936; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - "Probably Mrs. Brown": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1936; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - "The Rabble Rouser": McCall's Magazine, 1924; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - "Riplet, Try to be Nice!": Manuscript, undated; 2 folders Typed manuscript (Box 88, Folder 6-7)
    - Mr. Rumbin Stories, 1936-1945; 2 boxes
      - "Mr. Rumbin's Personal Romance": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1936; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - "El-mechun!": Saturday Evening Post, 1936; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - "What Price Goyor?": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1937; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - "Whose Copley?": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1937; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - "A little Deal in Irony": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1938; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - "Pat for Pit": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1938; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - "Connoisseuries": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1939; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - "Don't Sell It, Mr. Rumbin": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - "Mr. Rumbin's Dix Chunior": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - "Mr. Rumbin's Blessed Misforture": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1945; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - "The Fascinating Side of a Business": Manuscript, undated; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Susie Stories, 1931-1946; 3 boxes
      - "Susie's Little Play": Manuscript, Ladies Home Journal, 1935; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - "Partly Thirty-Five Years Old": Manuscript, Ladies Home Journal, 1935; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - "Goodness, Badness!": Manuscript, Ladies Home Journal, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - "Little Woman": Manuscript, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - "The Best Little Girl in the World": Manuscript, Ladies Home Journal, 1936; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - "Susie's Papaer's Old Sweetheart": Manuscript, Ladies Home Journal, 1936; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - "Susie the Big Little G-Man": Manuscript, Ladies Home Journal, 1937; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - "She was Right Once": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1931; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - "Stein Solitaire": Manuscript (unpublished), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - "Some People Have All the Luck": Manuscript, Liberty, 1946; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - "What the Lady Said to the Policeman": Manuscript, Saturday Evening Post, 1933; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - "When Youth is Beautiful": Manuscript, Woman's Home Companion, 1933; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - "The World is Mine": Manuscript, The American Magazine, 1944; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 1D: Short Story Collections, 1901-1935; 4 boxes
    Consists of manuscripts for collections of short stories, including "The Fascinating Stranger and Other Stories," "In the Arena," "Looking Forward and Others," "Mr. White, The Red Barn, Hell and Bridewater," and "The Works of Booth Tarkington."
    - The Fascinating Stranger and Other Stories, 1916-1927; 1 box
      - "The Fascinating Strangers": McCall's Magazine, 1922; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - "The Party": Red Book Magazine, 1921; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - "The One-Hundred Dollar Bill": Manuscript and GalleyMcCall's Magazine, 1923; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - "Jeanette": Red Book Magazine, 1921; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - "The Spring Concert": Red Book Magazine, 1921; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts, some signed (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - "Willamilla": Red Book Magazine, 1921; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - "The Only Child": Everybody's Magazine, 1917; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - "Ladies' Ways": Red Book Magazine, 1927; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - "Maytime in Marlow": Everybody's Magazine, 1916; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - "You": Red Book Magazine, 1922; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - "Us", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - "The Tiger": Red Book Magazine, 1921; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - In the Arena, 1901-1904; 1 box
      - "Boss Gorgett": Everybody's Magazine, 1903; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - "The Aliens": McClure's Magazine, 1904; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - "The Need of Money": Manscript, McClure's Magazine, 1904; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - "Great Men's Sons": Everybody's Magazine, 1901; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Looking Forward and Others, 1917-1926; 1 box
      - "Looking Forward to the Great Adventure": American Magazine, 1925; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - "Nipskillions": American Magazine, 1917; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - "The Hopeful Pressimist": Cincinatti Enquires, 1924; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts, signed (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - "Stars in the Dust-Heap": Metropolitan, 1917; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - "The Golden Age": American Magazine, 1926; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - "Happiness Now": American Magazine, 1925; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Mr. White, The Red Barn, Hell and Bridewater, 1927-1935; 1 box
      - "Mr. White", 1935; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Preface, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - "The Red Barn": Manuscript, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - "Hell": Saturday Evening Post, 1927; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - "Bridewater": Manuscript, undated; 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - "Bridewater", undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Blurb, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - The Works of Booth Tarkington (Autograph Edition), 1918; 1 box
      - Vol. VIII, Introduction to "Harlequin & Columbine", 1918; 1 folder Autograph manuscript, signed (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Vol. VIII, "Mary Smith", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript, signed (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Vol. VIII, "Truth is Stranger Than Fiction", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript, signed (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Vol. VIII, "Truth is Stranger Than Fiction", undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Vol. VIII, AMs, TMs, "Marjorie Jone's Picnic", dates not examined; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Vol. VIII, "Penrod - Zoologist", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Vol. VIII, "The Second Name", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Vol. VIII, "Brudie's Pickle", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Vol. IX, "Mr. Brooke", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Vol. IX, "Lord Jerningham", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 1E: Plays, 1893-1986; 34 boxes
    Consists of plays written by Booth Tarkington, including "Aromatic Aaron Burr," "The Gentleman from Indiana," and "The Ohio Lady," as well as others.
    - Aromatic Aaron Burr, 1938; 2 boxes
      - Prologue, Acting Script, and Reading Script, 1938; 7 folders Typed manuscript (Box 98, Folder 1-7)
      - Scripts for Each Character, undated; 12 folders Typed manuscript (Box 98, Folder 1-12)
      - Photographs of Garrick Players Company production in Kennebunkport, Maine, 1938; 1 folder (Box 98, Folder 13)
      - Aromatic Aaron Burr, 1938; 1 box (Box 99)
    - Beauty and the Horse Doctor: Script, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript, signed (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Beauty and the Jacobin: Galleys, Scripts, undated; 4 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 100, Folder 2-5)
    - Bill the Brute: Script, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Bimbo the Pirate: Script, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscripts (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Cameo Kirby: Scripts for Act I-IV, undated; 7 folders Typed manuscripts, some signed (Box 101, Folder 1-7)
    - Cinderella of Tomkins Square: Acts I-IV, undated; 2 folders Typed manuscripts, some signed (Box 102, Folder 1-2)
    - Clarence: Scripts for All Acts of the Play, undated; 2 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 102, Folder 3-4)
    - Colonel Satan: Scripts for All Acts of the Play, undated; 7 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 103, Folder 1-7)
    - Colonel Satan: Scripts for All Acts of the Play, Notes, undated; 10 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 104, Folder 1-10)
    - The Country Cousin, undated; 7 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 105, Folder 1-7)
    - Foreign Exchange (i.e. The Other Side: Nancy Baxter): Manuscript, undated; 6 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 106, Folder 1-6)
    - The Gentleman from Indiana: Manuscript, undated; 5 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 107, Folder 1-5)
    - The Ghost Story, 1922; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - The Gibson Upright: Manuscripts, Galleys, undated; 6 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts, some signed (Box 108, Folder 2-7)
    - His Word of Honor, undated; 4 folders Typed manuscript (Box 109, Folder 1-4)
    - The Honorable Julius Caesar, 1893-1919; 1 box
      - Programs, 1893-1919; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - Typed Manuscript, dates not examined; 2 folders (Box 110, Folder 2-3)
    - Hoosier's Abroad: Manuscript, undated; 4 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 110, Folder 4-7)
    - How's Your Health, 1929; 2 folders Typed manuscript (Box 110, Folder 8-9)
    - In the Borderland, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript, photostat (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - In the Chimney Corner (incomplete), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - The Intimate Strangers, 1921; 6 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 111, Folder 3-8)
    - Karabish: Manuscript, Programs, 1939; 4 folders Typed manuscript (Box 111, Folder 9-12)
    - The Kisses of Marjone: Manuscripts, Autographed Photostat, undated; 2 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 112, Folder 1-2)
      First published in John-a-Dreams, 1986 December.
    - Madam Sunshine: Act I, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Magnolia (Kunnel Blake), 1923; 10 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 114, Folder 1-10)
    - The Man from Home (The Guardian), 1907; 7 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts, photostat (Box 115, Folder 1-7)
    - The Man on Horseback, 1901; 9 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 116, Folder 1-9)
    - Monsieur Beaucaire, 1901; 14 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 117, Folder 1-14)
    - Mr. Antonio: Manuscript, 1916; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Mrs. Jim's Romance (If I Had Money, Getting a Polish), undated; 10 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 119, Folder 1-10)
    - The Ohio Lady, 1916; 5 folders Typed manuscript (Box 120, Folder 1-5)
    - Polderkin, 1895; 8 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 121, Folder 1-8)
    - The Prodigals, 1895; 6 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 122, Folder 1-6)
    - Queen Elizabeth and the Countess of Nottingham (unpublished), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Rose Briar, 1922; 7 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 123, Folder 2-8)
    - "Love and the Moon" Lyrics from Rose Briar, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - The Rose (unpublished), undated; 4 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts, some signed (Box 124, Folder 1-4)
    - The Rose, undated; 4 folders Typed manuscript (Box 125, Folder 1-4)
    - Springtime, 1909; 4 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 126, Folder 1-4)
    - Station YYYY: Manuscripts, Galley Proofs, 1926; 3 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 126, Folder 5-7)
    - Summer Covers (incomplete), undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - The Travellers: Manuscripts, Galley Proofs, 1925; 4 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 126, Folder 9-12)
    - The Trysting Place, 1922; 6 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 127, Folder 1-6)
    - Tweedlers, 1923; 6 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 128, Folder 1-6)
    - Up from Nowhere, 1919; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - The Wren, 1921; 2 folders Autograph manuscript (Box 129, Folder 2-3)
    - Your Humble Servant, 1908; 2 boxes
      - Typed Manuscript, 1908; 8 folders (Box 130, Folder 1-8)
      - Autograph and Typed Manuscripts, dates not examined; 4 folders (Box 131, Folder 1-4)
    - Unidentified Plays, dates not examined; 2 folders (Box 131, Folder 5-6)
  - Subseries 1F: Film Scenarios, dates not examined; 4 boxes
    Consists of manuscripts for film scenarios, including "The Millionaire" and "Pied Piper Malone," as well as others, some of which were unproduced.
    - Beaucaire (unproduced), 1921; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Edgar Scenarios, dates not examined; 2 boxes
      - Edgar and the Teacher's Pet, 1920; 1 folder Signed autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - Edgar Camps Out, 1920; 1 folder Signed autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 132, Folder 3)
      - Edgar Takes the Cake, 1920; 1 folder Signed autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 132, Folder 4)
      - Edgar the Detective, 1921; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 132, Folder 5)
      - Edgar the Explorer, 1921; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 132, Folder 6)
      - Edgar's Country Cousin, 1921; 1 folder Signed autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 132, Folder 7)
      - Edgar Feast Day, undated; 1 folder Signed autograph manuscripts (Box 132, Folder 8)